

A Journeyman Plumber with six years of experience, specializing in residential plumbing, water lines, septic systems, and contractor management. A strong history of executing installations and repairs for large home remodeling projects. Adept at I ead i ng a pp rent ice p I u m be rs and contractors to ensure q u a I ity deli verables.

Professional Experience

Plumbing Technician

Brooklyn Plumbing Co., New York, NY May 2018- Present

- Lead the installation and repair of plumbing systems, water lines, pipe fixtures, toilets, sinks, and drainage systems for home remodeling projects valued at up to \$100K
- Analyze blueprints to identify potential risksand project roadblocksand conduct inspections of piping systems to diagnose root causes
- Manage project teams of up to six apprentice plumbers, assigned responsibilities, prioritized project tasks, and ensure compliance with OSHA safety

Apprentice Plumber

Manhattan Plumbing Pros, New York, NY September 2016- May 2018

- Collaborated with plumbing technicians to install sinks, toilets, pipes, water heaters, and HVAC systems for 15+ clients per week
- Interfaced with customers to identify issues, provide recommendations for pipe replacements, and deliver high-quality customer service

123 Your Street, New York. NY 12345 fel icia gray@exa m pl e. co m (123) 456-7890

Education

Plumbing Technician Program Brooklyn Trade School, New York, NY Septem be r 2014 - May 2016

High School Diploma Utica High School, Utica, NY September 2010 - June 2014

Key Skills

- Residential Plumbing
- Dra i nage System s
- ♦ OSHA Safety
- HVAC
- Troubleshooting

Certifications

 Journeyman Plumber, State of New York, License #12345678, May 2018